

Viktorija Judeikyte

7444547898 · fjviktorija@gmail.com

Skills Self-motivation Conflict Resolution **Customer Service** Communication Skills Critical thinking and problem solving Time Management Leadership Skills **Decision Making** Teamwork Effective Time Management Communication Computer Skills Adaptability Microsoft Office Ability to Work in a Team Ability to Work Under Pressure Ability to Multitask Languages English Lithuanian

Russian

Profile

Self-motivated and creative Business Development Manager with 5 years experience in Aviation and Digital advertising Industries. Managed teams and executed various business relative bargains which increased business yearly revenue by 300%. Fundamental understanding and application of several programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JS and NodeJS. Known for superb communication skills, eye for detail, quick response in the presence of unforeseen challenges and ability to inspire and maintain exceptional relationships with colleagues and clients.

Employment History

Business Development Manager, Invoke. Vision, Birmingham

August 2019 - Present

Develop a growth strategy focused both on financial gain and business image.

Research and keep an eye on new opportunities in the market.

Build and keep long term partnerships with clients.

Prepare and perform sales agreements.

Finalize and keep records of revenue.

Arrange and plan business meetings.

Senior Cabin Crew, Gulf Air, Middle East, Bahrain

August 2018 - August 2019

In-charge of in-flight teamwork and responsibilities accomplishment whilst ensuring smooth communication and problem solving on board the aircraft.

Flight attendant manageer, Global airways

March 2017 - August 2018

Traveling and staying in the base of ongoing project in particular base. Responsible for staff well being and motivation on projects away. Helping to solve raised issues before or after flight. Working closely with the main office and reporting performance and general condition of ongoing project. Communicating with project partners.

Education

Certificate, Birmingham University

May 2021 - Present

Attending part-time studies at Birmingham university to gain more knowledge and qualification in coding.

Bachelor, Coventry University, Coventry

Hobbies

I am extremely energetic person and do not like to waste any time. I am interested in sports and have a few prizes in table tennis. I enjoy long summer days to spend playing volleyball outdoors and dance floor is not a new thing for me. As most of people I need me time and best way to get the energy back I spend while painting. Travelling always been a part of my life for this reason the best holidays I imagine when travelling locally or abroad! Even keeping myself busy I always find time to make a group meal and socialise with best friends and family members.

September 2017 — July 2020

Finished Coventry university and received a qualification in Aviation Management

Certificate, Baltic Aviation Academy

August 2015 — October 2015

Finished Baltic Aviation Academy and gained a qualification to work in Aviation Industry.